export const data = [
    {
        question: "Fill in the blank:",
        sentence: "We (go) .... to Turkey this weekend.",
        ans: "are going", // Correct answer
        ansType: "fill-in",
    },
    {
        question: "Fill in the blank: ",
        sentence: "Recently, my brother (find) .... a very good job.",
        ans: "found", // Correct answer
        ansType: "fill-in",
    },
    {
        question: "FIND THE MISTAKE AND WRITE IT BELOW:",
        sentence: "Many childrens go to school even on Saturdays.",
        ans: "childrens", // Mistake is 'childrens'
        mistake: "children",
        ansType: "error-identification",
    },
    {
        question: "FIND THE MISTAKE AND WRITE IT BELOW:",
        sentence: "Men never cannot cook.",
        ans: "cannot", // Mistake is 'cannot'
        mistake: "can",
        ansType: "error-identification",
    },
    {
        question: "Fill in the blank:'use should,must,need,have to'",
        sentence: "I (shart) .... wear uniform for school.",
        ans: "should", // Correct answer
        ansType: "fill-in",
    },
    {
        question: "Fill in the blank: ",
        sentence: "Many women .... get education in the past.",
        ans: "did not", // Correct answer
        ansType: "fill-in",
    },
    {
        question: "FIND THE MISTAKE AND WRITE IT BELOW:",
        sentence: "We need to know English very good.",
        ans: "good", // Mistake is 'good'
        mistake: "well",
        ansType: "error-identification",
    },
    {
        question: "Fill in the blank: ",
        sentence: "A study surveyed hundreds of types of birds in the USA and Canada. It found out that nearly a third of birds died from most biomes since 1970. That is almost three billion birds.\n" +
            "\n" +
            "\n" +
            "Biomes have killed almost ..... of all birds in the USA and Canada.",
        ans: "found out", // Mistake is 'found out'
        mistake: "found",
        ansType: "error-identification",
    },
    {
        question: "Fill in the blank: ",
        sentence: "Healthcare in Britain is getting worse, with long waiting lists and not enough doctors and nurses. Chloe Kirbyshire’s daughter has a serious eating problem, but Chloe has been waiting six months to see a specialist.\n" +
            "\n" +
            "Chloe needs a very good doctor for her ....",
        ans: "a third", // Correct answer
        ansType: "fill-in",
    },
    {
        question: "Fill in the blank:",
        sentence: "Pollution comes from industry, power plants and mostly cars. One piece of the matter is 30 times smaller than a human hair. \n" +
            "\n" +
            "The biggest reason for pollution is ....",
        ans: "daughter", // Correct answer
        ansType: "fill-in",
    },
    {
        question: "Fill in the blank:",
        sentence: "Mallorca put a strict ban on alcohol in some party zones in May. People can pay a fine of up to 1,500 Euros for breaking the rules. Luis moved to the area 25 years ago. He says that tourism changed a lot, and the noise is unbearable.\n" +
            "\n" +
            "Luis thinks that the .... in Mallorca is the worst now. ",
        ans: "cars", // Correct answer
        ansType: "fill-in",
    },
    {
        question: "Fill in the blank:",
        sentence: "Scientists tested four sunscreen products and their ingredients. Participants of the study applied sunscreen on their bodies for four days.\n" +
            "\n" +
            "The test took .... in total.",
        ans: "tourism", // Correct answer
        ansType: "fill-in",
    },
    {
        question: "Fill in the blank:",
        sentence: "Denmark’s capital Copenhagen started over 300 projects to protect the city from floods and extreme weather. A big flood in 2011 caused a lot of damage and the city decided to change many things. \n" +
            "\n" +
            "Copenhagen decided to change many things after the ....",
        ans: "four days", // Correct answer
        ansType: "fill-in",
    },
    {
        question: "Fill in the blank:",
        sentence: "The Enigma Machine was a cipher machine for Nazi Germany. During World War II, they used it to encrypt messages.\n" +
            "\n" +
            "The Enigma Machine was helpful in encrypting .... ",
        ans: "started", // Mistake is 'started'
        mistake: "started after",
        ansType: "error-identification",
    },
    {
        question: "Fill in the blank:",
        sentence: "Rescuers found two bodies in a sunken yacht near Sicily, Italy. The boat is 50 meters underwater, and divers have trouble getting inside because of floating objects. They are also using remote-controlled robots to help. \n" +
            "\n" +
            "Divers are helped by .... to make their work easier.",
        ans: "messages", // Correct answer
        ansType: "fill-in",
    }
];
